[panting]
Where is it?
I told you,
we don't wear locators.
[screams]
Wait.
Big toe, left foot.
[groans]
♪ tense music ♪
- Two minutes.
- [Tucker] Killing every one
of these motherfuckers.
- Clear.
[Meade]
They found the locator.
That's all they found.
Everybody breaks, Byron.
You know that.
And when she breaks,
who knows what spills out?
What happened to my wife?!
I'm sure you've discussed this.
- Worst-case scenarios.
- Is that what this is?
Spotter identified:
rooftop, far side street.
Driver's down.
This is my ride.
[gasps]
Wow, you're really...
- [gasps]
- [Kyle] In case you haven't
already figured it out,
you got a lot
of explaining to do.
[train brakes screeching]
[train whistle blows]
♪ tense, dramatic music ♪
[brakes squeal]
- [door opens and closes]
- [indistinct chatter]
[baby crying in distance]
[Cody J speaks Ukrainian]
[responds in Ukrainian]
Olga Balakin?
Tak.
[gasps]
[screams]
[muffled scream]
[gasps]
We're gonna get up
nice and easy.
Get up.
♪ urgent electronic music ♪
[panting]
Sit down.
We're clear.
A-Americans?
What you do?
Americans are our friends.
Maybe we're your friends.
[typing]
[computer beeps]
[young woman shuddering]
Do not speak unless spoken to.
Make no sound. You understand?
If you make any noise,
we will kill you.
[mutters]
You have picture?
We're up.
♪ tense, ominous music ♪
Move to the table
and sit, please.
[sighs]
Now, before
I start chopping body parts,
I want to make sure
we're in the right house.
Is that Mom?
Your little sister's a looker.
Boys are gonna have fun
with that one.
- What are you doing?
- I'm not
gonna waste my time
torturing you.
I know the training
you've been through.
I could shoot you full of all
the scopolamine I want.
You'd still lie to me.
Can't torture the truth
out of you either,
but I can...
torture it out of her.
What truth?
Well,
we got your boy in Ukraine.
About 48 hours later,
senior case officer
overseeing the mission
had two Russian contract agents
at her fucking front door
armed... with restraints.
Explain that.
I don't know
who's your case officer.
You met her at the fucking park.
You chose the park.
I didn't choose it.
You chose it.
You chose everything.
I'm not gonna do this with you.
[sighs]
Boys... [sighs] get a finger.
[screaming]
[whimpering]
Please, no.
Wait! Wait! Wait!
- They can't hear you.
- You can hear me.
What do you want to know?
How they made her?
Hold up, boys.
I don't know.
Maybe they got her face
from a drone or a satellite.
Then they'd have all of us.
And they didn't show up
at my fucking house.
How did you get
into the country?
Did you fly into Kiev?
Because the whole world
watches Kiev.
These are excuses, Oleksandra.
I don't want excuses.
I want fucking answers.
You round-tripping for Russia?
Ah. Double agent my ass.
You're a double agent,
but it ain't for fucking Ukraine
and it sure as hell
ain't for us.
My father died fighting Russia.
My brothers fight Russia
right now, today.
That is my nation, my home.
Soviet Union destroyed
my country.
Everybody starved.
Everybody was scared
to even think
because they read your mind
like a book,
but today's Russia,
this Russia is worse
because now they are rich
and they are free to spend it.
And you are acting
just like them.
You know, go ahead, kill them.
Big, tough fucking soldiers rape
an old woman
and a little girl and kill them?
Go ahead, do it.
Here, shoot me right here.
Come on, soldier girl,
shoot me right here.
You want to come kick me again?
Come kick.
You fucking try.
Boy, I tell you.
[chuckles]
These fucking Russians,
they're a different breed.
Don't you fucking call me that.
That's what you are.
You're a fucking Russian.
Never you call me that.
Fuck you!
Dirty fucking lying, scheming,
soulless fucking Russian.
[yells]
I'm going to fucking kill you!
[screams]
[yells]
[groans]
Oh, shit, that was fun!
[panting]
- Whoo!
- [Oleksandra panting]
[laughs]
I think I touched a nerve.
You don't know.
You don't know the monsters
and what they do. I know.
You think yours will be
the first soldiers to rape her?
Just the first Americans.
I think
we're all good here, boys.
Oleksandra.
My Oleksandra?
We needed proof
she is who she says she is,
and you were the proof.
Sorry for the inconvenience.
[door opens]
- Oleksandra.
- [door closes]
[sobbing]
The logical answer
to the question
of how our officer was outed...
...is you.
You understand that, right?
You get it?
Two contract agents knock
on her door.
Where are they now?
They were killed at the scene.
Now you're starting to
understand the way Russia works.
They didn't know who she is.
They suspect who she is,
and they sacrificed two lambs so
that she could prove who she is.
And now they know
because she told them.
That is how Russia plays.
Trust me.
If they wanted to take her,
she'd be gone.
See you in a little bit
for round two.
[door opens]
[footsteps retreating]
[door closes]
[Cruz sighs]
So what do you think?
What do you think?
Look, I ain't no fucking spy,
but that's not how I act
when I'm trying
to hide something.
We feeding her?
Water, bathroom break, anything?
Don't open that door unless
the team's here to move her.
If she opens that door herself,
you fucking shoot her.
She's chipped,
they'll know her location.
That's why we move her
and move her
and keep fucking moving her.
Look at all this tradecraft
you're learning.
You're gonna be a spy
in no time.
Your game is not my goal, buddy.
You're playing it anyway,
though, aren't you?
♪ dramatic, haunting music ♪
♪
[water running]
[sighs]
[Neal] There's not much here.
Your choices
- are cereal or cereal.
- [Joe] Yeah.
I'll go
to the supermarket later.
Everyone's up early.
Well, hour and a half commute
to school now.
That's assuming
we're still sending them?
Security will escort
and stay on location
until they're ready
- to return.
- [Neal] On location?
School's a location now.
- It was always a location.
- No, no, it had a location.
Everything has a location,
and now it is a location--
And what do you want me
to do about that?
- What I want you to--
- Can we just not fight?
I'm calling a family meeting.
[Joe] I'm gonna need some coffee
for a family meeting.
I'll get you your coffee.
[sighs]
Thanks.
♪ plaintive music ♪
[sets down mug]
Okay, let me have it.
We want you to quit.
What do you think
that's gonna solve?
Well, then there's no reason
to hurt you.
It doesn't...
It doesn't work like that.
Evil doesn't stop being evil
when we surrender to it.
It just gets more evil.
Girls.
I don't know what your passion
in life will be.
Your father's passion
is fighting to save lives.
My passion is fighting
to save a way of life.
Your father doesn't quit
when he loses a patient.
Of course, it hurts him
in more ways
than he'll ever be able
to express to you
or to me, but he doesn't quit.
And I've lost lives.
I've known many very,
very good people
who gave their lives
for this way of life
that we all get to enjoy.
And I've...
almost lost mine more than once.
And I may lose mine yet.
And, yes, I've taken lives.
I've killed
for this way of life.
But that's how precious
I believe your freedom is.
We've danced around this
forever,
and there's
no dancing around it anymore.
I'm a soldier,
and a soldier's job
is to fight until the soldier
is unable to fight
or until the fight is over.
And I believe that our right
to choose how we want
to live our lives
is worth the sacrifice.
[sighs]
That's how much I love you.
All of you.
[kisses]
I have something for you.
Can you come with me?
Yeah.
No, Joe, I can't.
We have an insurance policy
on the car.
That's all this is.
I can't.
Okay.
I'm sorry this followed me home.
I got to go to work.
Joe... Joe, just, what...
what does that mean for you?
After all this?
It means
finding the rest of them.
♪ pulsing, dramatic music
[door opens]
[helicopter blades whirring]
I got Randy and Two Cups
with your family
till we put together a detail.
Where's the detail from?
Ours, with O.S.
- Where to, boss?
- Office.
[engine starts]
[second engine starts]
♪
[Meade speaks indistinctly]
- [sighs] Morning.
- How are you feeling?
Uh, to be honest with you,
I am pretty fucking pissed off.
That's my girl.
How's the family?
They're rattled.
- I'd imagine.
- [sighs] Yeah.
- [knocking]
- Yeah.
- Have a seat.
- [door closes]
Well, her behavior
does not align
with being complicit
in the attempt to...
whatever they were trying to do.
And to be honest,
her explanation makes
as much sense, if not more,
than anything else
we've come up with.
What is her explanation?
The attack on Joe
is coincidental
to the operation in Ukraine.
[Westfield scoffs]
I mean, come on, Kyle.
They made the attempt
the day she returned,
20 minutes after she walked
through the front door.
Well, maybe
they had eyes on her in Kiev.
Maybe they'd had her
for a while.
But if they knew the mission,
and they had her the whole time,
they could've hit her
at any point.
Hit her team en route,
hit her on return,
hit her plane.
They don't own the air
over Kiev.
They don't have to.
It's not like they won't violate
Poland's airspace.
My guess?
They learned we had the package
after the package
was long fucking gone.
So they get two-man team
on every known case officer,
start shaking the trees,
- looking for anything.
- [scoffs]
Has Russian Foreign Ministry
reached out to State?
Have they made any indication
that they know we have it?
No.
I got to tell you,
whatever they know, they didn't
learn it from this double agent.
I had my hands
on her entire fucking family.
She didn't flinch,
she didn't beg.
She didn't bargain, plead,
deny, nothing.
Except try to claw my eyes out
for accusing her
of working with Russia,
and I mean come across
the table to tear my head off.
It was a completely irrational,
purely emotional reaction
motivated by just how much
this woman hates
- the fuck out of Russia.
- Is that your opinion?
[Meade] She's a Lioness, Joe.
She's not trained
in counterespionage
or interrogation or NLP.
She was under.
She was interrogated
while she was under.
She held her cover
and she completed her mission.
I would say
she's pretty trained.
And I'd very much like
her opinion.
What she does know, I...
I don't know.
What she did in that room,
she wasn't faking.
I want to talk to her.
Where is she now?
We're bouncing her.
I can cut her locator,
bring her in,
- but then she's out.
- No.
If we're not blown
and we pull her,
they'll add that math up
real quick. I want to see her.
- Where's the prize now?
- Should be at Gitmo by now.
Get me confirmation.
And get me an assessment
on our asset.
Are we believing this, or
are we dumping her in the river
and making a statement?
What are we doing?
And then what are we doing next?
And what are we doing
after that?
Yes, sir.
[Westfield]
Thank you.
- [door closes]
- What do you think?
A coincidence is
a conspiracy of the guilty.
Yurimov is a big prize.
Too big to use as bait.
That's my opinion.
We'll make her give us
another one.
So, do you work with my mom?
Is that a yes or no?
That's a
"he's not gonna tell us."
We work for you right now.
That's a fact?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Okay.
Then we're blowing off school
and going to Fair Oaks Mall.
[Randy]
Nice try, kid.
Bossy.
Like someone else I know.
Yeah, I bet she's got
a temper, too.
Yeah, she sure does, and you
meatheads are about to see it.
Called that one.
- [Randy] Yeah.
- The apple don't fall far.
[Randy]
No, it never does, does it?
[Two Cups]
No, sir, mm-mm.
Oh, what's this?
You got dispatch
in your ear, yeah?
Yeah, if it's an accident,
then it just happened.
Nobody called it in.
[horns honking]
[tires screech]
You see this fucking guy?
[horns honking]
♪ eerie music ♪
That's how I'd do it.
Let's do it.
[siren chirps]
[tires screech]
[siren chirping]
[Randy]
Hey.
Sirens mean fucking move. Okay.
Oh, that's cute.
Get the fuck out of here. Move.
Oh, he's getting out.
[Kate and Charlie scream]
- [tires screeching]
- [horns honking]
[Kate and Charlie panting]
Sorry, girls.
Probably nothing.
That didn't feel like nothing.
We're going too fast.
[panting]
Can you guys please
just slow down?
Please.
Please, can you just slow down?
♪ dramatic music ♪
We're on location. You got us?
[agent over radio]
We see you, Roadrunner.
Hold in the vehicle
until clear to proceed.
[tires screeching]
Clear to move.
Moving now.
[Oleksandra panting]
There are two elevators.
Elevator on the left.
- [elevator bell dings]
- [panting]
♪ uneasy music ♪
[clicks elevator button]
[elevator bell dings]
Never been on 24.
What's on 24?
Nothing. It isn't leased.
Looking to lease it?
Maybe.
Yeah? What's your business?
None of your business.
What's your business?
Why are you so interested
in hers? You-you know this guy?
Never seen him before.
Look, man,
I'm just trying to be nice.
[chuckles]
This is fucking Baltimore.
Nobody's trying to be nice.
[elevator bell dings]
Were you guys trying
to act shady?
Why not just say you're with the
management company or something?
'Cause what if he's
with the management company?
Never lie to strangers.
Only lie to people close to you.
Mm.
That's comforting.
Remind me never
to get close to either of you.
You know what the people
close to you know,
and you know who they know.
And who they don't.
[elevator bell dings]
[knocking]
Real nice.
She did it to herself.
[sighs]
Your people came to my house.
My house!
- Not my people.
- No? Oh.
What, did you retire from SVR
these past few weeks? Did you?
You know who my people are.
I'm not fucking
playing this game with you.
Whether they're your people
or your fucking cover,
they're still
your fucking people!
And your fucking people
came after me and my family!
Well, you know what they say.
A soldier's oath is
his family's oath.
[grunts]
[breathing sharply]
That's not the saying here.
Did you give them
a little nibble?
Did you tell them something
to make them happy?
'Cause that's your game, right?
They found you on their own,
I'm telling you.
If they knew
you were the one who took him,
then they must know
your mission.
If they knew your mission,
you would have never returned.
Who has my phone?
Well, I'm sure
you're watching it.
Has my brother called?
Has he texted "Let's catch up"?
Huh?
That's how they call me in.
You haven't received that text.
They don't know it was you.
They think Ukraine.
They think he's still there.
So now you tell them
you have him,
'cause you have him,
and all the hornets come out.
And I show you the hornets.
You'd better.
[Joe sighs]
Take her home.
Let her clean up.
Then meet me at the farm.
My number's in it.
We start now.
[knocking]
[door opens]
[door closes]
Why are you sitting outside?
You'll get sunburned.
Doctor says half hour a day,
vitamin D.
Honey,
don't they have a pill for that?
Not the same.
You need UV rays
to synthesize it
in the skin cells.
Then why do they sell the pill?
[chuckles]
Gee, honey, I wonder.
[Meade]
Religion, religion,
uh... trade routes?
[scoffs]
Oil.
Another way
to explain it would be,
Islamic state, Islamic state,
authoritarian state,
Communist state.
Speaking of which, question...
...regarding foreign
intelligence stateside.
Question for me or from me?
We have zero counterintelligence
activities stateside.
Every bit of it is handled
by the FBI and the NCSC.
You guys are woven into FBI
pretty tight, I thought.
For cover, sure.
- So what's the question?
- Mm.
I fancy that you're
a pretty attractive target
for a foreign
intelligence group.
I would agree
with that assessment.
So I assume
they've attempted it.
Many times.
Care to guess how?
Shell companies
hiring your firm.
Mm-hmm.
Lawsuits on behalf
of companies and NGOs,
uh, various
contract negotiations
that might expose
other contract negotiations.
Maybe attractive
flight attendants
conveniently beside you
at a bar.
It's everything you do overseas,
- just done here.
- Mm-hmm.
They love
State Department officials
and congressmen on their second
divorce and cash-strapped,
Russia in particular.
China plays
a very different game.
Their focus is
information theft,
cash-leveraging,
and the long game.
China's playing a 50-year plan
first implemented
in the mid-'60s.
And the 50-year plan is now.
What would possibly be
the reason
for U.S. government officials
not to investigate
the origins of a disease,
let's say,
a testing lab in Wuhan
funded by U.S. dollars?
Why would a U.S. government
agency be partnering
with a known adversary
on a Chinese institute
of virology,
particularly one
that President Obama defunded,
based on the risks
of gain-of-function testing,
in 2014?
And yet the funds still flowed
to that facility.
How many
U.S. government officials
were under Chinese control
or influence
to facilitate that?
China doesn't waste its time
trying to flip
FBI counterterrorism agents
or military officers.
That's Russia's sphere
because Russia's greatest fear
is war.
China has no fear of war
because
they have absolutely no interest
in military conflict.
Our nations are
too economically interwoven.
China's plan is for the United
States to be at war with itself,
at least intellectually.
China's trying
to win the war of information,
and they are.
And you fear China more?
I wouldn't say that.
I would say
I fear them the same
for very different reasons.
Here.
♪ ominous music ♪
[water running]
[exhales, sniffles]
[exhales]
[throws away paper towel]
[typing]
[chips crunching]
[door opens and closes]
[Randy clears throat]
[Joe sighs]
[sighs]
So,
what we do
and what she does are similar,
at least in terms of tradecraft.
Identify a target,
make contact,
earn their confidence.
The similarities end there
because our objectives
are different.
We eliminate targets.
She mines information.
This is Oleksandra.
It's a mouthful.
How do you feel about "Alex"?
Oleksa.
I'll take it.
Oleksa is a Ukrainian
Foreign Intelligence
Services officer.
She has been embedded
in the Russian SVR since 2018.
- Say that three times fast.
- Shut the fuck up.
Oh! Goddamn it. Fuck.
- I'm sorry.
- [clears throat]
- A comment?
- No, ma'am.
Her intelligence led
to our successful extraction
of Aleksi Yurimov from Ukraine.
[Bobby]
Also maybe the two Russians
on your front porch.
[sighs heavily]
Just saying.
[sniffles]
Kyle?
She's been vetted.
[Oleksandra]
She's right to question.
Question everyone
and everything they do and say.
You tell one lie to achieve
your objective, we tell ten.
Then we change the objective
and tell ten more.
It's all lies now.
How the fuck do you know
what we do?
She's Lioness.
And she's the Lioness
who befriended al-Zarqawi's
third wife
and provided his location
to your Special Forces,
who then attacked his motorcade
and called a missile strike
that killed al-Zarqawi
and the wife she befriended.
[Oleksandra]
We know what you do.
China knows what you do
and when you do it.
But since
you don't do it to them,
they don't care.
Here's how it's explained
in Russia.
Russia's a wolf pack.
China is the tiger.
And you?
You are the bear.
Wolf pack cannot kill the bear.
The bear's too big,
even for a pack.
And the tiger cannot kill
the bear alone.
Wolf pack and the tiger
cannot play nicely together,
so they don't play at all.
So how do they fight you?
What kills the bear?
Disease kills the bear.
And they've been infecting you
for many years.
And in your packet
are the Americans
with the disease.
What value does
the superintendent
of a school have
from an intelligence standpoint?
[Oleksandra]
He controls curriculum.
Disease doesn't begin
in the heart. It ends there.
You find him at a country club,
a nightclub, seduce him,
photograph it, and you own him.
Go to an army town.
Go to a strip club
near Fort Bragg,
Fort Benning, Fort Campbell.
Where do those girls come from?
They come from Russia, China,
Venezuela, Colombia.
Sometimes it's your girls,
Americans.
They're desperate already,
or they wouldn't be dancing
for money.
Money's easy.
Russia has money.
Russia has your money.
They print it.
So does China.
So does everyone.
[Amber]
Everything
- she said is fact.
- [Tucker] Yeah.
We all know about the honeypot.
Although the methodologies
of the biggest players vary,
their approaches
are essentially the same.
Biggest players,
in case you don't know:
Russia, China, Qatar,
Muslim Brotherhood--
although they cannot be assigned
a nation--
Iran, and then
to a lesser degree,
you have North Korea, Venezuela,
most Gulf states,
and then some Russian proxies.
This pyramid represents
the general philosophy
of clandestine operations
against the U.S.
The broadest and least
direct action of the pyramid
is disinformation
and disruption.
Typically players
on this level are dumb,
which is just to say
that they have no knowledge
of their involvement.
This is funding organizations
on any side
of the political spectrum
to place consistent pressure
on state and local resources
through protest.
Organizations that specialize
in crowd agitation
receive substantial funding.
The focus is on disruption
of traffic routes.
A particular focus, though,
is paid
on disruption at universities.
Above that is essentially
information-bombing
on social media.
And then above that
is your entry-level espionage
involving direct
foreign influence.
This can be done through
low-level contract agents
at said universities
or through direct agitation
and suppression of individuals
on social media.
Above that is where
your real tradecraft begins.
Gain leverage
on an individual.
Typically,
this is done financially,
but oftentimes you have
overt target manipulation:
honeypotting,
as you just called it,
and then blackmail
into assisting.
This happens to researchers
in virtually any field but
particularly those researchers
that oversee projects
at universities,
defense industry employees,
and any federal employee
above a GS-12
because it is very likely
they have broad access
to federal databases.
Oh, pardon me.
I'm just a dumb
helicopter pilot,
so I have no idea what the hell
you're talking about.
What is this honeypot?
You don't know
what a honeypot is?
Do you know what a honeypot is?
Of course
I know what a honeypot is.
What?
[Joe]
A foreign agent either seduces
or drugs a target.
Sexual acts with that target
are recorded,
and those images are used
to bribe that individual
into cooperation.
[Randy clears throat]
We all know
the places to avoid
and where's safe,
so what's
with the fucking lecture?
Look.
Most of these are
very low-level, we know this.
We're gonna flip 'em over
to the FBI.
They can make examples of it,
they can fucking ignore it.
I don't fucking care.
What I do care about is
which computer analysts
at the NSA did they honeypot?
Which senator, which White House
senior staff member,
which governor,
what fucking news anchor?
Okay? We're big-game hunting.
Let me ask, um, a question.
Yeah.
Some stripper
or bottle service girl
or whatever honeypots
a Green Beret. How--
Why does it got to be
a Green Beret?
Uh, it's just
a hypothetical, bud.
Well, I-I've noticed
your hypothetical
ain't with your old
fucking SEAL team.
Just as long as it's not Army.
Hey, you know,
fine, make it a Marine.
- How's that?
- [Two Cups and Bobby] Yes.
- The fuck it's a Marine.
- [Two Cups] There you go.
[Tex] Okay, great. I'm just
saying Green Beret would be
the most likely
to get a honeypot.
Most... most likely?
Oh, motherfucker.
You want to get
a handle on your team?
- [overlapping chatter]
- [Joe] This is soldier shit.
You got to let 'em work it out.
Otherwise it just festers.
Don't you dare say
my fucking unit.
[Tucker] Why's it got
to be a soldier at all?
Why can't it be that-that
dipshit on the school board?
- [Two Cups] Yeah, there you go.
- This asshole.
This guy, okay?
Make it this fucking guy.
Jesus Christ.
Real crack unit
you got here, Joe.
Real crack unit.
[laughs]
All right, you got a guy
on a school board,
gets honeypotted by some woman.
The stripper isn't managing
the asset. Who is?
At a lower level,
a case officer is assigned.
And at a higher level,
at my level,
I maintain the asset.
Any of these yours... Oleksa?
- No.
- What's yours?
We're not concerned about hers
right now, not yet.
Why not right now?
Well, because she's still under.
[Two Cups]
Your second tier
on your pyramid there,
the information bombing.
Are we talking about,
you know,
direct-action disinformation?
Or can-can we couple that
with misinformation?
[Amber] It's really just
anything to cloud the truth,
- fundamentally.
- Yeah.
[Amber]
I mean, you-you can see...
[Joe sighs]
She's still under.
So she says.
Why?
What possible benefit
does that serve for us?
- Keeps them from killing her.
- [sighs]
Then we WitPro her.
Or we don't.
And we trot her out
on national television
and we scream it
from the rooftops.
- Have you seen her asset list?
- [sighs]
Have you?
Yeah. Yeah, I've seen it.
- And, Kyle?
- [scoffs]
You know
I can't tell you that, Joe.
You got the same clearance I do.
- Go to SAC and request it.
- Spare me
the three fucking hours
of bullshit, would you?
You're gonna have
to look at it yourself,
but it's pretty fucking heavy.
Just tell me, Kyle.
You already said it yourself.
Someone from NSA.
JSOC.
[sighs]
Senator.
Senator?
Did you count
how many times I nodded?
I counted five.
And that is why
we can't out her.
'Cause the fucking sky falls.
Well, isn't that the goal?
Maybe.
You comfortable with the price?
The entire country doubting
the-the allegiance
of every elected official
in government?
Well, turn on the fucking news,
Kyle, we're already there.
I want
to run it up the flagpole.
- Well, look, I don't--
- Will you back me up on this?
I don't think putting her
on the news is the play,
but there may be a way to run
the rats out of the outhouse--
Well, why don't we just
discuss that en route?
You got it.
[Amber speaking indistinctly]
- You keep that woman here, okay?
- We putting her in custody?
Well, let's call it
unofficial custody.
She does not leave. She has
to go fucking take a piss,
- the whole team goes with her.
- Roger that.
♪ unsettling music ♪
♪
[Meade]
Come on in.
Evening.
What do you got, Joe?
[sighs]
We're allowing Oleksandra
to stay under?
- [Meade] Mm-hmm.
- Correct.
What is the tactical purpose
of that?
Have you seen her dossier
of gets?
- I have not, sir.
- Pretty impressive haul.
[clears throat]
Has information or votes
they cast benefited Russia
since she snagged them?
[Westfield]
No, not in any manner
our analysts can determine, no.
All five have
publicly supported Ukraine
and voted in favor
of each aid package
Congress has introduced.
Which isn't surprising, Joe.
Her allegiance is to Ukraine.
She's not going
to knowingly bring material harm
to her nation.
How were the assets obtained?
Four were soft, one was hard.
How soft and how hard?
[Meade]
Campaign funds for two,
heavy investment
in one's district,
and the spouse of another
runs an investment firm.
She married that firm
to a Russian investment fund.
The fourth,
the old-fashioned way.
- [Kyle exhales]
- [Westfield] It's not our job
to walk you through intel, Joe.
I think we should inform Russia
that we have their agent.
We're waiting on their call.
If we reach out, it alludes
to an interest in negotiating.
It gives them leverage.
Not the one we took.
Let them know we have her.
And inform them
through a statement
by the press secretary.
♪ mysterious music ♪
No names, no pictures,
just a statement
that says we have apprehended
a Russian agent on U.S. soil
who has made contact
with numerous U.S. officials
and has appeared
to have used extortion
to coerce
some of those officials.
We tell them it's early
in the investigation,
and for national security,
no other information
will be released at this time.
It allows us to present
a posture of knowing everything.
What they imagine we know
will be much more
than what
we have actually ascertained.
[Kyle] It's never the crime that
gets you, it's the cover-up.
And they will try
to cover everything.
It's Whac-A-Mole, but
they're all coming out at once.
[Joe]
And we will
already have the mallet out.
What about Mrs. Ukraine?
Turn her loose and stay close.
Every contact
she has will reach out.
Every SVR agent in the region
will reach out, too.
Hunting mice by setting the barn
on fire, so to speak.
Yes, ma'am.
Of course, at the end of that,
well, you have no barn.
Who cares? It wasn't our barn
to begin with.
It's rather callous
towards our new friend.
She used us from the beginning.
We let her use us.
We used her right back.
Why stop now?
[sighs]
You will never convince me
the men at my home found me
through satellite footage
from an airport.
They were told who,
they were told where,
and they were told when.
Either she did it
or she knows who did it.
They think of themselves
as wolves.
Fine, let's throw her back
to the wolves... and find out.
Let me sleep on it.
Thank you.
[door opens]
Which way you think
he'll go on this?
He's already decided.
Eh, I think he's 50-50.
You don't sleep on a "no."
[press secretary]
Yesterday evening,
FBI counterintelligence agents
apprehended an agent
of the Russian
Foreign Intelligence Service,
or SVR as it is known
to the intelligence community.
The U.S. Attorney's Office
is preparing espionage charges
stemming from evidence
implicating the agent in both
bribery schemes
and extortion schemes
against U.S.
government officials,
as well as state
and local government officials,
as well as U.S. citizens
in the private sector
in both the defense industry,
as well as the information
technologies industry.
We are withholding all names
as the investigation is ongoing.
Yes?
Where is this individual
being held?
I can't release
that information.
When will the suspect
be arraigned?
That is a question
for the attorney general.
Is the attorney general
planning a press conference?
We don't have that information
at this time.
- ♪
- [dialogue inaudible]
♪ sinister, jarring music ♪
[squeaking]
[grunting softly]
- ♪
- [dialogue inaudible]
[Joe breathes heavily]
♪